to promote me
I'm bringing a context to ask you
we just got here on the big beach
get a ride
that today we will stick
at a fair in São Paulo thank you speak brother
and there smooth
caraca didn't even ask to see anything bro in one of those
we could have brought
brownie for sale
or that gives hand time
but angels can fly
that's it bro we have to get
people who understand about process acceleration
of operation
how can we scale this
and talk to people who have
this expertise to pass us
to have a little greater understanding right guy
seeing the safe environment there
what is the follow-up
of you we are looking for
actually the understanding
how we can accelerate
Charlie Brown's sales are on
optimize and accelerate sales if you have any idea
I came here for you
promote
I'm bringing a context to ask you
and we created a brand
called
Charlie Brown and Junior
are Brown in Rottweiler shape
original taste
Pinker has a belonging
in the city of Santos where we are in more than
twenty points of sale
and what we came to do here in the main
is to exchange an idea to try to see how we can
accelerate
to put on big gondolas shelves
supermarkets
how to be more interesting than self-serving
in order to attract
whales not minnows
you arrive with a hut
of such a presentation you will need to sell
the facility
of the process so that he can
deliver to his client's hand
c starts to generate what for him value of his store
you enter another level of business
guy congratulations on the work
run away from those who run
on your side and those who love you this is the purest thing
oh people i got a lot of insight here now at the fair
i'm understanding more or less like the parade
works
I think I'm getting an idea here brother
may he get a right malandro tio
but the video is ending
tamo together valeu
bora Charlie Brown
Calm world style,
there are people who resent a lack of